

PROFILE

I am an experienced Web developer & Human resources management specialist. I have many work experiences for more than 5 years with different companies using various platforms and languages, I have also gained practical knowledge regarding customer service as a consequence of working within many domains. I aspire to work in an environment that encourages me to succeed and grow professionally where I can utilize my skills and knowledge appropriately.

CONTACT

PHONE: +971-559901857

FACEBOOK: Facebook.Jafar-aji

EMAIL: jafaraji769@gmail.com

EDUCATION

Tishreen University 2015 - 2020Informatics engineering
GPA **75**

JAFAR AJI

Front End Web Developer & Human resources management specialist

WORK EXPERIENCE

TradeValley

Front-end developer/ Team Leader (2021–2022)
Web developer and designer using Basic Html, CSS, JavaScript,
bootstrap, and many platforms like WordPress and did a lot of email
templates. I have developed the whole company website pages in
one month and designed more than 100 email templates.

Digital Edge

Front-end developer/ Team Leader (2019–2021)
Web developer and designer using Basic Html (CSS)

Web developer and designer using Basic Html, CSS, JavaScript bootstrap, and many platforms such as OpenCart, WordPress, and Shopify. Also, I have been a manager for the Frontend team and we had a lot of achievements like we finished a complete 3 websites in one month.

Syrian pioneer

Gaming designing trainer (2017–2019)

I have had professional course training using Unity3D for more than 3 groups and we created a 3D game at the end of the course.

FreeLancer

Web developer, Designer, Online Services **(2018–2021)** I provided many online services like Front end Developer and Converting Images to PDF and Word.

Golden Group

Agent and representative of the company (2018–2019)
I was a customer service of the sales department in the company.

AL Nada Hospital

Customer Service Supervisor (2018–2021)

I provided customer service supervisor in the hospital and worked to meet and assist customers and solve problems that they or the work team might encounter.

TECHNICAL & MANAGEMENT SKILLS

- * Search Engine Optimization (SEO)
- * Project Planning
- * Task Management
- * Version Control (Git)
- * Content Management Systems (CMS)
- * CSS Preprocessors (Sass)
- ★ UI/UX design programs (Photoshop, Gimp)
- * Decision-making skills
- * Employee Relations Management (ERM)
- * Human Resources Experience

SOFT SKILLS

- * Commitment and accepting responsibility.
- * Work under pressure.
- * Creative Problem Solving.
- * Team Leadership (Motivation, Delegation, Organization).
- * Self-motivated.
- * Ability to work in groups.
- * Good communication with people.

REFERENCE

* Mr. Kahtan Ibrahim

General Manager of **MegaSoft** Global Training Center.

PHONE NUM: +963 946 686 000

As. Mariam Ali Atallah

General Manager of Syrian Pioneers Center.

PHONE NUM: +963 999 240 378

ACHIEVEMENTS & AWARDS

- ✓ Diploma in Human Resource Management (HRM) from MEGA SOFT INTERNATIONAL TRAINING ESTABLISHMENT.
- Certification in Web Design and Development using (React Js) and (Next Js) is from the Syrian Scientific Society for Informatics.
- Certification in web development and design using HTML, CSS, bootstrap ,Tailwind ,JavaScript, and jQuery from Udemy Online Courses.
- Qualified Certification as a Front-End Developer from Digital Edge Company.
- Qualified Certification in Started with ReactJS Components from Simplilearn online courses.
- Certification in using WordPress platform for Web developing and designing from Udemy online courses.
- Certification in using the Open Cart platform from Udemy online courses.
- Certification in Search Engine Optimization Complete Specialization from Udemy Online Course.
- Certification in Soft Skills from Skills and Careers Center in Tishreen University.
- Certification in Effective work team from Syrian Pioneer Foundation.
- Certification in Responding to emergencies, first aid, and basic firefighting from Syrian Pioneer Foundation.

LANGUAGES

Arabic	100%	
English	0007	
English	80%	